# Masum Billah



masum.billah78@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/mbillah-cse



+8801922483273



https://masumbillah.github.io/portfolio/



Experienced Web Development with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Javascript, Jquery, React js, Vue.js, Angular Js, Meteor js, Node js, Laravel, Mysql, Mongodb, Apollo client, Github, Bitbucket, AWS service, Digital Ocean server, Rest API, etc. Strong engineering professional graduated from Dhaka International University.

# **Experience**

#### Full-stack Developer

Battery Low Interactive Ltd.

Jan 2021 - Present (2 year 7 months +)

Here, my responsibility is full-stack development. Basically I'm working with PHP latest framework Laravel, Mysql, Node, Express, Mongodb, Postgresql, React is, Vue is, Vuetify, Angular is, aws services, firebase etc. Implement applications:

- 01. Frontend, Backend and rest api(every things) of https://togumogu.com/
- 02. Frontend & Backend of https://motorcycles.runnerautomobiles.com, https://runnermotors.com.bd
- 03. Frontend, Backend and rest api(every things) of https://send-dev.buddyandselly.com
- 04. Frontend, Backend and rest api(every things) of https://thefinancialexpress.com.bd
- 05. Completed Some our govt. private applications. It's govt's secret applications

### Sr. Web Developer

Gain Solutions Ltd

Oct 2014 - Dec 2020 (6 years 3 months)

I worked here javascript, node js, react js, react hooks, redux, vue js. Meteor js, Mongo db. Graphql and etc.

- 01. Gain CRM Now it's closed
- 02. Uniteliving It's a property management system application.

https://uniteliving.com/



#### **Executive of TV News**

Ryans Computers Ltd.

Jan 2010 - Apr 2014 (4 years 4 months)

My responsibility was TV News monitor and reporting

#### **Education**



Dhaka International University

BSc in CSE 2009 - 2013



# Jhenaidah Polytechnic Institute, Jhenaidah

Diploma in CSE 2005 - 2009

## **Skills**

JavaScript • Reactjs • Node.js • ReactHooks • Vue.js • HTML5 • CSS3 • SASS • Git • vue js • Laravel • Angular.js • mysql • Rest API • Mongodb • Postgresql • Express • Digital Ocean • AWS service and etc